<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<presenters>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Practical and Applied Technology in Hollywood
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Matt Lewis
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Production Engineer 
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/MattLewis.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Before a career in the studio system, Matthew Lewis was an enthusiastic member of the hacker 
				community of the early 1990s. After a few run-ins with the law and a successful dot com-era startup, Matthew
				was snatched up by Universal Pictures as a part of a studio-wide effort to adapt the marketing of motion 
				pictures into the digital era. Starting on films like <i>American Pie</i> and <i>The Mummy</i>, Matthew has 
				spent the last 14 years leveraging his technical background with his production experience into an unusual career 
				of blowing up buildings, tracking reality-show contestants in remote areas, and even creating massive interactive 
				darkhouse-ride experiences for films like <i>Resident Evil</i>. Matthew's talk will go behind the scenes into the 
				practical application of technology in Hollywood &mdash; with never before seen engineering data, photos and video 
				of the creation of some of Hollywood's most popular franchises. This talk is not about CGI or computer-generated 
				animation; instead, the focus will be on real-world technology used on-set in the world of high-end production, 
				including modern vehicle manipulation, pyrotechnics, set design, costume design and a plethora of critical 
				off-camera technologies.</p><a name="PamelaThompson" id="PamelaThompson"></a>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			To Get Work, Network: Learn the Art of Networking from a Top Recruiter in Animation and Visual Effects
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Pamela Thompson
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Speaker/Recruiter
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/PamelaThompson.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Pamela Kleibrink Thompson is a popular speaker at colleges, film festivals and entertainment 
				industry conferences around the world.  Recent speaking engagements include presentations at Ferris Media 
				Festival in Michigan; Jalloo in New Brunswick, Canada; Cineposium in Boise, Idaho; ADAPT in Montreal; the 
				MDA Animation Workshop in Singapore; FMX in Stuttgart, Germany; KAFI in Kalamazoo, Michigan; and schools 
				such as Ringling and Savannah College of Art and Design.  She has presented courses at SIGGRAPH in San 
				Diego, Boston, and Los Angeles; was a noontime lecturer at Disney Feature Animation; and taught the Career 
				Realities course at Gnomon School of Visual Effects in Hollywood.</p>
				<p>Thompson is an internationally-acclaimed recruiter, career coach and animation veteran (production manager 
				on Emmy Award-winning The Simpsons, ink and paint supervisor on Paramount’s animated feature Bebe’s kids).  
				She was named one of the Top Ten Recruiters by Animation Magazine.  Recruiting clients include Disney, Fox 
				Animation, The Embassy VFX, Lucas Animation, and Framestore.</p>
				<p>Pamela Thompson’s monthly column, The Career Coach, appears at the Animation World Network web site
				http://mag.awn.com.  She has written articles for over 40 other publications, including  Animation Today,  L
				os Angeles Times, Entrepreneur, Idaho Women’s Journal and Woman’s Day.<a name="FonDavis" id="FonDavis"></a></p>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			How Computers Did Not Kill Practical Effects
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Fon Davis
			</presentername>
			<title>
				CG Artist, Founder, Fonco Creative Services
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/FonDavis.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>In his two decade career, Fon Davis has worked on over 30 feature films. As an alumnus of the 
				Industrial Light and Magic Model Shop, Fon has worked on features such as:</p>
				<ul>
					<li><i>Star Wars</i></li>
					<li><i>Pearl Harbor</i></li>
					<li><i>Starship Troopers</i></li>
					<li><i>Galaxy Quest</i></li>
					<li><i>Terminator III</i></li>
					<li><i>Mission Impossible III</i> </li>
					<li>and the <i>Matrix</i> series.</li> 
				</ul>	
				<p>In addition to his work in visual effects, Fon has also worked in Disney’s art departments as a concept 
				designer/model maker, and on several stop motion projects including <i>The Nightmare Before Christmas</i> 
				and <i>Coraline</i>. More recently, Fon was the Miniatures Supervisor on both <i>Big Miracle</i> with 
				Drew Barrymore, and also on Neill Blomkamp’s recent feature, <i>Elysium</i>. Having started Fonco Creative 
				Services in 2000, Fon also writes and develops his own projects, frequently using his CG skills alongside 
				practical model making. With his vast experience, Fon is well-placed to discuss the art and craft of model 
				making for cinema, from concept design to hybrid practical and cgi effects, with a particular expertise 
				in knowing where models and miniatures can play a role in today’s digital world.
				<a name="PatrickBass" id="PatrickBass"></a></p>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Business skills and professional development for IT and INFOSEC Pros
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Patrick Bass
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Director of Security Solutions, Terra Verde Services
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/PatrickBass.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Patrick Bass is the Director of Security Solutions at Terra Verde Services where he leads the 
				firm’s Managed Security and Professional Service groups. His forthright and direct approach resonates strongly 
				with a tech savvy generation. For over 16 years, he has led data and physical security organizations as a 
				motivational and business-minded executive leader.</p>
				<p>Patrick knows how to address security risk from a technology and business perspective.  He is the former chief 
				security officer for a major credit card processor and has worked in leadership roles within IBM, Banner Health, 
				and Element Payment Services to name a few.  He creates enterprise security solutions for organizations with 
				stringent security requirements and compliance mandates for regulatory standards such as PCI, HIPAA, and SOX.  
				Patrick has exceptional analytical capability and is able to make calm, rational decisions in the face of multiple 
				competing priorities, high stress, and emergent situations. He has strong management skills and is able to work 
				with diverse groups in a highly effective manner.</p>
				<p>His educational accomplishments include an undergraduate degree in Information Technology Security, an MBA in 
				management and strategy, and a Master’s degree in Information Assurance and Security.  Currently, he is working on 
				an applied research doctorate and preparing for a dissertation focused on mobile security. Patrick holds a number 
				of professional/industry certifications including: CISSP-ISSP/ISSMP, CISA, CEH, CHFI, G2700, CCENT, PCIP, and CGEIT.</p>
				<a name="BeitsLivneh" id="BeitsLivneh"></a>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Be Your Own Boss? Yeah… Right! 
		</presentationtitle>	
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Beits Livneh
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Owner, Click Computer Services
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/BeitsLivneh.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Back in 1996, Beits was assisting with IT related projects during his 
				service in the Intelligence Branch, Israel Defense Forces. After his three years of 
				mandatory service, he was offered a job at a Microsoft college in Israel, where he 
				worked as a system administrator. In 2000, Beits moved to Arizona, with lots of ambitions 
				and absolutely no grey hair (yet). Fast forward to 2013, Beits is now married with 6-year-old 
				triplets, a 4-year-old daughter, three businesses and still lots of entrepreneurial ambitions.</p>
				<p>The primary business that Beits owns and operates is an IT consulting firm called Click 
				Computer Services (CCS). CCS struggles with one main challenge in the past nine years, finding 
				team members who share the same values, work ethics and knowledge that the industry needs so badly.</p>
				<p>Established in 2004, CCS now employs eight team members, and is one of Arizona’s most reputable 
				IT consulting firms which focuses on small business technology, Cloud/Hosted service and in-house 
				IT services.</p><a name="GodricJohnson" id="GodricJohnson"></a>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Jetstreame: An Independent Game Studio
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Godric Johnson
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Producer/Creative Director, Jetstreme
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/GodricJohnson.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Godric Johnson is an American artist, game designer, and musician from Baton Rouge, 
				LA. He is the TRUE founder of Game-hop (his brand/style and music) and holds a bachelor's degree 
				in Game Design and Digital Art from University of Advancing Technology.  Having a vibrant passion 
				for both video games and music, his young career spans from doing game design and concept art for 
				Artificial Life Inc to performing at GDC, Gam3rcon, DigiFEST South, and various other conferences.  
				He's an active member of the IGDA chapter in Baton Rouge, and mentors local high school students 
				interested in the gaming industry.  In his free time he loves to draw, play games, create music, 
				perform at events, and host fighting game tournaments such as Quarter Circle Forward (QCF).  He now 
				currently serves as the Producer/Creative Director of the independent game studio Jetstreame.</p>
				<a name="WayneNeale" id="WayneNeale"></a>
			]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			UX Rock 'n Roll Style: What Can We Learn About User Experience Design from Music?
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Wayne Neale
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Founder and President, Kydak
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/WayneNeale.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Wayne is currently the founder and President of Kydak, a user experience design company. 
				Kydak uses user research, design and usability evaluation methods to solve complex problems and 
				create innovative experiences for digital software products. Prior to Kydak, Wayne held executive 
				positions at SAP, ShoppingScout, Khimetrics, ITax Group, Kodak and was the co-founder of iZoom.com and 
				Fairway Productions. Wayne is co-chair of IxDA (Interaction Design Association of Phoenix) and founder 
				of Phoenix UX.  Wayne was part of a team and only website that was inducted into the Smithsonian 
				Institution’s National Museum of American History with “24 hours in Cyberspace” in 1996. Vice President 
				Al Gore unveiled the exhibit on January 23, 1997. Dr. Neale holds a Ph.D. in Human-Computer Interaction 
				from Virginia Tech, masters in human factors from California State University, Northridge and bachelors 
				in cognitive psychology from California State University, Long Beach.<a name="BenKoenig" id="BenKoenig">
				</a></p>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Security Operations: Incident Response
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Ben Koenig
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Sr Security Analyst / Team Lead
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/BenKoenig.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Ben Koenig, CISSP GCIH GCIA, is the Lead incident handler for Charles Schwab & Co., 
				providing guidance and leadership on the Security Operations Incident Response team. With over 
				14 years of Information Technology Operations experience, he has covered almost all areas of IT 
				Operations from alert monitoring to compliance and regulatory remediation. Whether configuring 
				firewall rules or conducting full incident response investigations, Ben's ability to quickly 
				identify and react to the given situation has been the cornerstone to many a team’s success. Prior 
				to working for Charles Schwab &amp; Co., Ben worked as the Lead Security Analyst for GoDaddy in 
				Scottsdale, Az. It was in that position that Ben learned the art of &quot;Drinking from the fire hose!&quot;, 
				a skill that serves all incident handlers well. Before joining the GoDaddy team Ben worked for 
				EarthLink, an ISP based out of Atlanta, GA, with various roles within IT Operations. This is where 
				Ben initially honed his skills in trouble shooting and analysis.</p>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			You Have an Awesome Idea for an App; How Do You Transform it into a Commercial Product?
		</presentationtitle>	
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Isac Artzi
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Partner, Thumb Magic, LLC
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/IsacArtzi.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Isac has over 20 years of experience in college instruction, adult learning, technology 
				development, and business entrepreneurship within a wide range of industries, markets, and disciplines. 
				Isac’s professional career spans military training and instruction, research, teaching, and educational 
				software development. At Michigan State University Isac directed the BioSci Explorer and Multimedia 
				Physics multimedia eLearning projects. At Gilat Communications, Ltd. Isac managed satellite-based distance 
				learning projects in Thailand, Australia, Israel and other countries. Isac was a computer programmer and 
				technology evangelist in Silicon Valley working with several Internet companies. While at AppStream (acquired 
				by Symantec) Isac worked on several intellectual property initiatives and was co-inventor on two software 
				streaming patents. Currently Isac is an Instructional Designer at Grand Canyon University, as well as an 
				Associate Professor at University of Advancing Technology. Isac is also conducting research in the area of 
				self-adapting eLearning environments and their business applications. His education includes undergraduate 
				and doctoral degrees in Computer Science &amp; Mathematics, Instructional Design, and Business.</p>
				<a name="ArthurVincie" id="ArthurVincie"></a>]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			World Building on a Budget: Techniques for Indie Sci-Fi Filmmakers
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Arthur Vincie
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Producer
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/ArthurVincie.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Arthur has over 10 years of film and television production experience as a line producer, 
				producer and director. He recently wrote and directed <i>Found In Time</i>, a sci-fi feature, 
				which won the Best Sci-Fi Feature award at the Shriekfest Film Festival, and is an official selection 
				at:
				<ul>
					<li>the Eerie Horror Fest</li>
					<li>Tri-Cities International Fantasy Film Festival</li>
					<li>Boston Science Fiction Festival</li>
					<li>Nevermore Film Festival</li>
					<li>International Horror/Sci-Fi Festival</li>
					<li>Imagine Film Festival of Amsterdam and </li>
					<li>the GenCon Indy Film Festival</li>
				</ul>
				<p>It will be released on DVD, streaming and VOD by Green Apple Entertainment.  
				Focal Press just published his non-fiction book on preproduction, <i>Preparing For Takeoff: Preproduction 
				for the Independent Filmmaker</i>.</p>
				<p><i>Caleb's Door</i>, Arthur's first feature, is available on DVD and VOD through distributor Around 
				The Scenes.  His short films <i>The Prayer Tree</i>, <i>Matter</i>, <i>Mornir/Mornen</i>, <i>Secret Language</i> have screened at various 
				festivals and art venues. </p>
				<p>Arthur has line produced or production managed several feature films, including: 
				<ul>
					<li><i>Helena From The Wedding</i></li>
					<li><i>Goodbye Baby</i></li>
					<li><i>Windows</i></li>
				</ul>
				<p>He has also post supervised: </p>
				<ul>
					<li><i>Rock the Paint</i></li>
					<li><i>The Toe Tactic</i>, directed by acclaimed animator Emily Hubley</li>
					<li><i>Racing Daylight</i> starring David Strathairn and Melissa Leo</li>
					<li><i>Company K</i></li>
					<li><i>The Reawakening</i> directed by Native American Diane Fraher.</li>  
				</ul>
				<p>These films have screened at the Tribeca, Slamdance, Nantucket, SXSW, Rome, Woodstock, and other film festivals, 
				and have gone on to theatrical, DVD and cable distribution.  In addition to features, Arthur has line produced 
				industrials, music videos, short films, spec commercials and other projects.</p>
				<p>In 2007, Arthur founded Chaotic Sequence Inc., which focuses on producing shorts and features.  To date the 
				company has production managed several short films and other projects, as well as <i>Found In Time</i>.</p>
				<p>Prior to line producing, Arthur worked in just about every department, for ABC, NBC, BBC America, MSNBC, the 
				Knitting Factory and various independent production companies in the New York City area.</p>
				<p>Arthur has written articles on budgeting and postproduction for Indie Slate and Student Filmmaker magazines, 
				and has guest lectured at New York University, the School of Visual Arts, CUNY/Hunter College, Brooklyn College, 
				and Fairleigh Dickinson University.  He currently teaches film production management at Montclair State University.  
				He holds a B.F.A. in Film/Television Production from New York University.</p><a name="JacquelineFebvre" id="JacquelineFebvre"></a>
				]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			New Utopia? How Design can change our world.
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Jacqueline Febvre
			</presentername>
			<title>
				General Director, Epcc ESAD (Ecole Supérieure d'Art et de Design d'Orléans) Orleans Higher School of Art and Design
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/JacquelineFebvre.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[ <p> Postgraduated in History of technology and graduated from ANAT (National Textile Art University), 
				Jacqueline Febvre is currently the General Director of the Epcc ESAD Orleans Higher School of Art and Design 
				(300 students, 55 teachers).</p>
				<p>She previously led from 1991 to 2001, the APCI (Agency for the Promotion of Industrial Creation) in Paris. 
				In this context, she led an important action program on design exhibitions, conferences and contests, publication 
				of books and magazines (exhibtion such as “Design, mirror of the century”, guides like France Panorama design, 
				competitions, creation of Design Observer). She began her career by creating and running a textile company and 
				was Deputy Director of School of Applied Arts, School of Fontblanche in South of France.</p>
				<p>She has been teaching History of Design (ISD Valenciennes, EDNA Nantes), is a speaker, and is an author of 
				numerous guides and articles on design project. She designed several important exhibitions like &quot;Changing Era&quot;
				(Museum of Science and Industry, Paris, October 2006&ndash;August 2007) of which she was co-curator with Thierry 
				Kazazian. She has conducted various research techniques History of the changing role of the designer between 1939 
				and 2000.<a name="JordanWomack" id="JordanWomack"></a></p>
			]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Implanting the Swarm in a Live Host: Mechanics for Shipping a Global Game Expansion
		</presentationtitle>	
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Jordan Womack
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Game Producer, Blizzard Entertainment
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[ <img src="Images/Speakers/JordanWomack.jpg" /> ]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Jordan Womack is a Game Producer at Blizzard Entertainment. He has been with Blizzard for 
				five years, shipping games as a QA lead and as a Producer; he has credits on <i>World of WarCraft: Wrath 
				of the Lich King</i>, <i>StarCraft II: Wings of Liberty</i>, and <i>StarCraft II: Heart of the Swarm</i>. 
				Before Blizzard, Jordan spent seven years as a project manager in corporate facilities and construction. 
				He switched industries to follow his lifelong passion for gaming, determined to work with the smartest 
				people on the biggest projects. Game development at Blizzard is exactly that.</p>
				<p>These days Jordan mainly produces engineering teams on <i>StarCraft II: Legacy of the Void</i> and on 
				Blizzard's upcoming action-RTS title, as well as supporting feature releases for the live <i>StarCraft II</i> 
				service. His scope includes:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>online game and social systems</li>
					<li>core game engine</li>
					<li>technical art and tools pipeline</li>
					<li>graphics engine</li>
					<li>and user interface</li>
				</ul>	
				<p>Jordan’s job as a producer is to turn goals into project plans and help teams execute them throughout design, 
				implementation and release. </p>
				<p>Jordan’s talk is about the details and the major challenges Blizzard faced and their specific logistical 
				and technical solutions for globally sim-shipping <i>Heart of the Swarm</i> to a live game service.</p>
				<a name="AnastasiosMaragiannis" id="AnastasiosMaragiannis"></a>
				]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			Design Futures: Technology in an Age of Uncertainty
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Anastasios Maragiannis
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Academic Portfolio Leader, University of Greenwich 
			</title>
			<image>
				<![CDATA[<img src="Images/Speakers/AnastasiosMaragiannis.jpg" />]]>
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[
				<p>Anastasios Maragiannis is the Academic Portfolio Leader in the Design Futures Department, School of 
				Architecture, Design and Construction, University of Greenwich, London, UK. He is a conceptual thinker 
				and design practitioner. Informed by design theory, his practice-based research focuses on how 
				computational technologies impact on the existing principles and forms of static typography and text. 
				His current work explores how innovative processes of design evolve within creative media, scrutinising 
				in particular how forms of typographic design expand into innovative technologies, virtual space and 
				interactive, sonic and animated components.</p>
				<p>Anastasios has presented his research and practice-based work in various international conferences and 
				in numerous places including the British Film Institute and the V&amp;A museum. He is member of the Digital 
				Research In Humanities and the Arts (DRHA) International conference standing committee; board member of 
				The Thursday Club, Goldsmiths, University of London and he has been awarded with the &quot;University of Greenwich
				Recognition Award&quot; as the &quot;Staff Member of the Year&quot;.</p><a name="RickRavenell" id="RickRavenell"></a>
				]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
	<presentations>
		<presentationtitle>
			UAT Alumni Panel: Life on the Outside
		</presentationtitle>
		<speaker>
			<presentername>
				Rick Ravenell
			</presentername>
			<title>
				Freelance Artist
			</title>
			<image>
				
			</image>
			<bio>
				<![CDATA[<p>Rick’s visual effects career started in 2008 at MKVFX where he was a compositor and 
				motion graphics artist on NBC’s Knight Rider.  Rick then went to Prime Focus for graphics work on 
				Avatar and he has been a freelance artist ever since. He has worked in television, commercials and 
				feature film for companies such as:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Digital Domain</li>
					<li>FuseFX</li>
					<li>Sabertooth Interactive</li>
					<li>Technicolor</li>
					<li>Zoic</li>
					<li>Encore Hollywood</li>
					<li>and most recently Svengali Fx.</li>
				</ul>
			]]>
			</bio>
		</speaker>
	</presentations>
</presenters>